{
    "id": "891e292430004aa3bfaf1a95a215dc18",
    "title": "Direct And Indirect Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The girl said that it ..................................... her great pleasure to be there that evening.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gives",
                "gave",
                "would give"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca9d802d8a1f4d2f856204ba4f488076"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ........................................... that he must go as soon as possible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "asked",
                "told"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "61bc3ffad8524a85b5b030036c76fdbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ........................................... to see any of them and asked them to go away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not want",
                "does not want",
                "had not wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b28a4838b264424ab56fb0ea6762990"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher says that if you work hard you .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will pass",
                "would pass"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9b339a93fc240418bdcd1daffe26a9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "has won",
                "had won"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f9e16f16701e4781bd7ba68efed91bed"
        },
        {
            "question": "He proposed that they ....................................... wait for her return.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "will",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "63d6adfe5aff428f80d786968a0249ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice exclaimed how clever .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was she",
                "she was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d367d85b9cf140f78b3dacd6357f87c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The young man asked which way she ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "had gone",
                "would go"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a89f73fe32847c2a0bed46dcd9ffe8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me where .................................... going.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I was",
                "was I",
                "I am"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "86babe1b68c34913a18b13b4868a13f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She requested them to wait there till she ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returns",
                "returned",
                "will return"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98ff34f8c1934734913a08f62d96ca3b"
        }
    ]
}